http://wp.dol.ca/webportal/parish/web/privacy/1/81

Contact UsBulletinMinistriesNews & EventsPrayer & WorshipSacramentsYouth
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices in relation to the collection, use, and storage of information that you may provide via this website as well as the use of materials provided on the site. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information.
Your Consent By using this Site, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information via this Site you consent to the: (i) collection, use, disclosure and storage of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and (ii) receipt of emails about us and our activities from time to time.
Information Management Like many websites, this Site collects information from its visitors by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail. Some of the information that you submit may be personally identifiable information (that is, information that can be uniquely identified with you, such as your full name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and so on). You consent to us using the information you have submitted to contact you in relation to those inquiries.
Links to Other Websites This Site may contain links or references to other websites. Please be aware that we do not control other websites and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every website you visit.
How to Contact Us If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this Site, please contact the Director of Communications.
Changes to This Privacy Policy If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this Site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information.
| E-mail Us
St. Clement Parish | E-mail Us
St. Joseph Parish | E-mail Us
St. Joseph Parish | E-mail Us
St. Mary Parish | E-mail Us
St. Michael And Sacred Heart Catholic Parishes | E-mail Us
St. Benedict Parish | E-mail Us
Blessed Sacrament Parish | E-mail Us
and St. John The Baptist Parish and St. Simon And St. Jude Parish and Holy Name Of Jesus Parish and St. John De Brebeuf And Companions Parish and Sacred Heart Parish and St. Mary Parish and St. Michael Parish and Ste. Anne Parish and St. Peter Parish and Our Lady Of Mount Carmel Parish and St. James Parish Seaforth and St. Peter's Parish and Holy Name Of Mary Parish and St. Boniface Parish and Our Lady Of Sorrows Parish and St. Ladislaus Hungarian Catholic Community and St. Casimir Parish and Sacred Heart Parish and Sacred Heart Parish and St. Mary Parish and Holy Cross Polish Catholic Community and Our Lady Of Victory Polish Catholic Community and St. Joseph Parish and St. Mary Parish and St. Patrick Parish and Paroisse Immaculée Conception & Saint-Philippe Parish and St. Francis Xavier Parish and Holy Family Parish and Our Lady Help Of Christians Parish and Holy Cross Parish and Mary Immaculate Parish and Our Lady Of Czestochowa Parish and Our Lady Of Siluva Lithuanian Catholic Community and St. Andrew The Apostle Parish and St. George Parish and St. John The Divine Parish and St. Justin's Parish and St. Leopold Mandic Parish and St. Francis-St. Martin Catholic Parish and St. Mary Parish and St. Michael Parish and St. Patrick Parish and St. Peter's Cathedral Basilica and St. Stephen Of Hungary Hungarian Catholic Community and Sacred Heart Parish and St. Patrick Parish and Sacred Heart Parish and All Saints Parish and Holy Angels Parish and St. Anne Parish and St. Mary Parish and Queen Of Peace Catholic Community and Paroisse St-Thomas D'Aquin and St. Joseph Parish and St. Christopher Parish and St. Philip Parish and Sacred Heart Parish and Assumption Parish and Our Lady Of The Atonement Parish and Holy Trinity Parish and Our Lady Of Guadalupe Parish and Our Lady Of Mount Carmel Parish and Our Lady Of Perpetual Help Parish and Most Precious Blood Parish and St. Alphonsus Parish and St. Angela Merici Parish and St. Anthony Of Padua Parish and Sts. Cyril And Methodius Parish and St. Francis Of Assisi Parish and Paroisse St. Jerome and St. John Vianney Parish and St. Michael Parish and St. Patrick Parish and St. Paul Parish and St. Theresa Parish and Kent Area Portuguese Mission and St. Charles Garnier Parish and St. Joseph Parish and St. Andrew Kim Korean Catholic Community (160) and St. Francis Of Assisi Hispanic Catholic Community and Middlesex And Lambton Portuguese Mission and St. Gabriel Mission (0539) and St. Michael Church and St. Philippe And St. Anne Vietnamese Martyrs Catholic Community (611) and Christ The King Church and Sacred Heart and St. Anne's Conception Church and St. George's Hungarian Byzantine Rite Parish and St. George's Ukrainian Catholic Church and St. Mary (Hungarian) Parish and Sts. Vladimir And Olga Church and Holy Dormition Monastery Chapel and St. Peter Maronite Catholic Church and St. Anthony's Maronite Catholic Church and St. Charbel Monastery and Sisters Adorers Of The Precious Blood (R.P.B.) and Sisters Of The Holy Names Of Jesus And Mary (S.N.J.M.) and Franciscan Sisters Of Immaculate Conception (S.F.B.Z.) and Sisters Of St. Joseph (C.S.J.) and Ursuline Sisters Of Agonizing Heart Of Jesus (USAHJ) and Ursuline Religious Of The Chatham Union and Sisters Of Service (S.O.S.) and Brothers Of St. Louis (C.S.A.) and Madonna House and Holy Family Retreat House (Oxley) and Medaille Retreat House and Holy Childhood Association and Marriage Encounter and Ministry To Priests and Diocesan Mission Commission and Director Of Priests' Personnel & Diaconal Ministry and Refugees International and Separated And Divorced Catholics and St. Stephen's Centre and Vocations Office and Holy Childhood Association and Society Of St. Peter The Apostle and St. Peter's Seminary and Assumption University Riverside Campus and Brescia University College and King's University College and John XXIII Centre and Xavier Resource Centre and St. Joseph's High School (ST) and St. Thomas Of Villanova High School and St. Anne High School and Cardinal Carter High School and Ecole Secondaire L'Essor and Brant Haldimand Norfolk C.D.S.B. and Huron-Perth Catholic District School Board and St. Michael's Secondary School and Ursuline College Chatham Catholic Secondary School and St. Patrick's Catholic High School and London District Catholic School Board and Catholic Central High School (L) and John Paul II Secondary School and Monseigneur Bruyere and Regina Mundi College and St. Thomas Aquinas High School and Windsor-Essex R.C.S.S. and Assumption College High School and Catholic Central High School (W) and F.J. Brennan High School and Holy Names High School and St. Joseph's High School (W) and E.J. Lajeunesse High School and St. Peter Parish and St. Joseph's Health Care, St. Joseph's Campus and
and Roman Catholic Cemeteries Of Windsor and
and
and Communications Office and Save A Family Plan and Office Of Canonical Services and Liturgical Commission and Director Of Personnel and
and
and
and Ministry Of The Deaf And Hard Of Hearing and Ecumenical Commission and Refugees Inland and Office Of French Translation and
and
and
and
and
and
and
and
and
and London Health Sciences, University Campus and
and Hotel-Dieu Site Hospital and Communauté Catholique Ste Marguerite D'Youville and St. Anne's Catholic High School and Metropolitan Windsor Nursing Homes and Ecole Secondaire De Pain Court/Secondary School and Ecole Secondaire St-Francois Xavier and St. Christopher Catholic Secondary School and London Health Sciences, Westminster Campus
and St. Joseph's Health Care, Mount Hope Campus and London Psychiatric Hospital and Windsor Regional Hospital (Metropolitan Campus) and Institute Of Pastoral And Educational Ministry (Assumption) and St. Mary's High School and Parkwood Hospital and Chatham-Kent Health Alliance and Bluewater Health and London Health Sciences, Victoria Campus and Sarnia General Hospital and Windsor Regional Hospital, Western Campus and Windsor Regional Hospital, Malden Park Campus and Ecoles Catholiques Due Sud-Ouest and U.S.A.H.J. London House and St. Clair C.D.S.B. and Holy Trinity Catholic High School and Immaculate Heart Parish and St. Thomas Psychiatric Hospital and Our Lady Of The Holy Rosary Vietnamese Catholic Community (164) and Diocesan Finance Committee and Diocesan Building Commission and Diocesan Loan Fund and
and Diocesan Audit Committee and Diocesan Investment Committee and
and Nat. Fed. Of Council Of Priests (Central Region) and Deanery Captains and Parish Stewardship Committee - 2004 and Deans/Episcopal Vicars and Parish Pastoral Council Chairs and Parish Finance Committee Chairs and Diocesan Centre (Administration) and Information Systems Services and Dio Net Internet Service Users and Dio Net - Church Of Our Lady, Guelph and Bishop's House and Catholic Cemeteries Diocese Of London Head Office and Diocesan Technology Advisory Committee and Michaelite Fathers and Chelsea House Basilians and Ecole Secondaire Ste Marie and Mother Teresa and Holy Cross High School and Diocesan Vocation Committee and NFPC and NFPC Executive and Office Of Campus Ministry At King's University College and Hotel-Dieu Grace Hospital and St. Joseph Hospital and
and Office Of Canonical Services Windsor Office and St. Elias Parish and St. Michael Byzantine Parish and Holy Family Chaldean Parish and
and San Juan Diego Of Guadalupe Hispanic Catholic Community and Council Of Priests and Diocesan Stewardship Committee - 2004 and Auxiliary Bishop's Office Diocese Of London and Diocesan Financial Strategic Plan and Planned Giving and Chancery Support Team and Catholic Family Services Windsor-Essex County and Diocesan Clergy Salary Committee and Diocesan Music Committee and Diocesan R.C.I.A. Committee and Directors Of Education and Religion Co-Ordinator and EDAS Team and Christ The King University Parish and Holy Trinity Parish and Holy Family Parish and St. Joseph Parish and Heart-Links and Visitation Parish and Corpus Christi Parish and Our Lady, Queen Of Martyrs Parish and Sacred Heart Villa and Royal Oak Long Term Care and St. Josephine Bakhita African-Caribbean Catholic Community and Windsor Regional Hospital and St. Joseph's Health Care and Diocesan Centre (Pastoral Leadership) and St. Peter's Institute For Catholic Formation and North American Martyrs Parish and Diocese Of London Migrant Ministry and Roman Catholic Campus Ministry University Of Windsor and Good Shepherd Parish and Holy Redeemer Parish and St. Daniel Comboni African Catholic Community and St. Bernard Of Clairvaux Parish and Assumption Heritage Fund Office and St. Isadore Parish are
part of the Roman Catholic http://www.dol.ca
Photos/graphics may not be reproduced without permission.
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use | Pastoral Plan & DioCMS Login
